<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="compatibility_lookup_table_horoscope_com_0">
        <item>Two personalities governed by the planet Mars are liable to lock horns frequently in combat. Each clearly stakes out a personal territory, a turf where the Aries individuality is asserted, and it requires the unconditional respect of the other. Harmony can reign only in the presence of a powerful, shared ideal which acts to channel the awesome energy of each and unites their strengths instead of opposing them. Together, they can generate megawatts! The love which binds them is impulsive, fiery, and impatient.</item>
        <item>One drives the couple forward; the other stabilizes it. Aries rushes in with enthusiasm, whereas Taurus takes the time to think and slows the pair down. In bed, these differences make for a spicy and passionate relationship. The former finds needed common sense and security with the latter, whereas the latter delights in the former\'s spontaneity and fury… as long as Aries doesn\'t upset the other\'s daily routine too much, or arouse jealousy.</item>
        <item>A promise of great excitement and entertainment! Both signs are endowed with good cheer and optimism, which makes them perfect pals. Life together is like an ongoing party, highlighted by flashes of imagination and friendship with others. Gemini easily adapts to the demanding Aries character, while Aries finds his or her partner to be an inexhaustible source of fresh air. The couple lives for the moment, with scarcely a care for tomorrow, but this continual improvisation is not the stuff of which lasting ties are made. Stay tuned for more adventures…</item>
        <item>Sensitive, gentle, subtle Cancer is likely to be offended by the Ram\'s sometimes brutal impulsiveness. One worships the family; the other feels hemmed in by it. Dynamic Aries resents being tied down to the home and hearth primordial to Cancer, and Cancer is likely to withdraw into a prolonged sulk if he or she feels abandoned. Only shared compromise, patience, and attentiveness can build this couple. However, the Aries will always be the boss.</item>
        <item>Aries decides, but the Lion rules. Each must be careful not to offend the other\'s vanity, because the most trivial events can become power struggles. However, the ardor and passion which animate both Fire signs may weld the two individuals into a radiant couple. Adventure, creativity, and success are on the horizon. Love is a matter of tenderness, desire, and submission. But perfect harmony will require respect for Leo\'s pride.</item>
        <item>Virtual opposites: The Virgo is a diligent worker, a faithful partner, and a born organizer; sparkling Aries lacks ongoing commitment but has pizzazz. He may sometimes chafe under Virgo\'s critical gaze. The Ram will dominate the pair, and his or her unpredictability will wreak havoc with Virgo\'s plans. But Virgo gives backbone to the Ram\'s impulses, and guides him or her with valuable advice. The alchemy of opposites forges a constructive but continually strained relationship.</item>
        <item>Two signs which naturally attract and complement each other. Tactful Libra tones down the Ram\'s fury, and redirects his or her individualism towards a partnership whose logical conclusion is the marriage which matters so much to Libra. The Libran harvests the Ram\'s vigor, but is sometimes rebuffed by blunt language. Aries must be careful to give Libra time to express him or herself. Otherwise, the magnetism which attracts them may turn into mutual repulsion.</item>
        <item>A bond between these two Mars-ruled signs is ardent, passionate, and often stormy. No neutrality is possible, and day-to-day management of such extreme feelings may prove difficult. Scorpio\'s possessiveness will not tolerate the slightest unfaithfulness, but the Ram often yields fully to the Scorpion\'s sensuality - unless he or she is startled into scampering away… This poignant dance, in which each partner vies for control, can be fleeting or long-lasting, sublime or terrifying: there is no happy medium!</item>
        <item>Two Fire signs soar with shared exaltation towards ambitious ideals and adventure. The Sagittarian\'s candor puts the Ram in his or her place if necessary, and communication flows readily between the two, limiting the damage from conflict. Energetic and intimate activity is part of their daily routine. These two individuals have energy to burn, and an appetite for mutual love and seduction. No clouds on the horizon as long as each accepts that the other will make no compromise…</item>
        <item>Can a fiery rebel and a practical Earth sign ever reach an understanding? They speak different languages: one held aloft by dreams while the other has his or her feet firmly on the ground. When they know how to reinforce the Ram\'s audacity with the Goat\'s constructive spirit, they can accomplish great things. Capricorn is slow to be tamed and won over, a process which Aries tends to interrupt early if he or she does not control his or her impulsiveness. However, if Capricorn\'s love is allowed to ripen, the other can luxuriate in it forever.</item>
        <item>Two forward-looking individuals who instinctively understand each other and share a vision of the future, as long as the freedom of each is respected. Aquarius is immune to the Ram\'s domineering spirit. But the Air sign\'s detachment may frustrate the Aries need for passion. If a common interest favors friendship over love and the Ram is satisfied with a dispassionate relationship, while Aquarius gains by the ardent contact with an Aries, the relationship they build will be healthy, fresh, and beneficial.</item>
        <item>Pisces has a fleeting and almost solitary spirit which may provoke the Aries authoritarian tendencies, and the two signs do not soothe each other. Pisces readily submits to domination, since he or she is awash in an inner world where reality has little effect. The vitality of Aries provides needed security. The couple will function if the Ram surrounds the Pisces with constant affection. If not, the Fish will spawn elsewhere, without even turning around for a final farewell.</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="compatibility_lookup_table_horoscope_com_1">
        <item>One drives the couple forward; the other stabilizes it. Aries rushes in with enthusiasm, whereas Taurus takes the time to think and slows the pair down. In bed, these differences make for a spicy and passionate relationship. The former finds needed common sense and security with the latter, whereas the latter delights in the former\'s spontaneity and fury… as long as Aries doesn\'t upset the other\'s daily routine too much, or arouse jealousy.</item>
        <item>This is a solid couple (if such a thing exists), loyal and sensual, whose moral and physical love is ruled by the goddess Venus. A shared taste for luxury, culture, beautiful possessions, nature, and material prosperity convinces each that he or she has chosen the best match. Nothing is accidental, and every event is carefully thought out. Although the legendary Taurus stubbornness can become a source of conflict, there are no other obstacles to a serene and long-lasting commitment. In fact, it may even be a little too serene.</item>
        <item>Gemini is a sociable, gregarious extrovert who loves the bustle of the city, while Taurus is quiet, quaint, and rural. The Bull seeks comfort and tranquillity, whereas Gemini\'s phone is always ringing, much to his or her delight. These fundamental differences may generate misunderstanding and conflict, aggravated by Taurean obstinacy. But the Taurus is easily enchanted by Gemini\'s liveliness, and Gemini finds a Taurus partner provides the security and stability he or she lacks.</item>
        <item>Could this be the ideal couple? Both partners are unabashed homebodies, delighting in simple pleasures: family life, good food, comfort, and prosperity. They cook up their own candlelight dinners, enjoy quiet evenings alone together, and plan their investments wisely, whether they\'re financial or personal. Mutual enrichment, comfort, and support are virtually guaranteed. They form a self-sufficient couple, a world unto themselves… as long as their home is comfortable and attractive!</item>
        <item>Birds of a feather flock together, and these two signs have a great deal in common. Deep down, they are erudite, sensual, sensitive, and artistic. Mutual contact reinforces the talent of each. But the extravagant Lion may clash with the discreet and thrifty Bull, and if Leo does not temper his or her selfishness, the Taurean partner will feel hurt. The couple, which is stormy in the intimacy of the bedroom, cannot weather daily life unless each makes a continual effort to accommodate the other.</item>
        <item>Two Earth-ruled signs which value tranquillity and discretion, they have all the ingredients for a harmonious love affair. Anxious Virgo finds reassurance in the stolid Bull, whereas the Taurean derives needed peace and energy from the Virgoan. A caress, a gaze, a gesture: each is worth a thousand words, when it comes to expressing the tenderness that binds them together. Taurus dominates, to the delight of clinging vine Virgo. "The power of harmony, and the deep power of joy…"</item>
        <item>The fact that both signs are influenced by amorous Venus gives their relationship a romantic and sensual outlook. But the sociable Libran\'s appetite for entertainment and conversation may be stifled by the Bull\'s stolid contentment with home and hearth. If the charm is broken, the Libra will soar alone. Moreover, Taurean inarticulateness may repel loquacious Libra. Yet with a little flexibility and subtlety, if these two partners want their relationship to last, it can!</item>
        <item>There\'s a lot of attraction in this match between two naturally reserved, determined, and physically oriented signs, and great potential for domestic success. Both value financial prosperity and hard work. But if they don\'t make beautiful music together immediately, a terrible uproar is imminent. Intuitive, emotional Scorpio accumulates negative feelings until they reach critical mass. If Taurus is not ready to handle a meltdown, Scorpio\'s tenacity will be unbearable and even the Bull will give up. It\'s either heaven or hell: nothing in between.</item>
        <item>One dwells in dreamland while the other never takes off from reality; one loves escape, travel, and change while the other doggedly takes root and slowly builds a real accomplishment. Flexible Sagittarius is more adaptable than the stubborn Bull, because he or she uses his or her powers of abstraction as an escape hatch. But each lives in a world alien to the other, and real understanding is a remote possibility. Their fundamental differences are likely to surface one day, perhaps forcefully enough to disunite them.</item>
        <item>Courageous, ambitious Earth signs, Taurus and Capricorn seem to be made for each other. Both value financial success and share a love of beauty, of lasting, classical foundations. Capricorn\'s irony charms the Bull, while the latter\'s expert sensuality rescues the Capricorn from his or her natural modesty. They enjoy talking together, and communication is excellent. They confide in each other, promising never to offend or betray the other. This could be a perfect couple.</item>
        <item>Love at first sight is probable, but can it ripen into a lasting love affair? Aquarius has an appetite for freedom and a gaze firmly turned toward the future. The possessive Taurean derives his or her pleasures from immutable values like the land, the family, and the past. If the present brings them together, they rarely evolve in the same direction together, and each will tend to stick to his own character. Soon the Bull feels misunderstood, while the Aquarian dreams of new horizons… But love makes anything possible!</item>
        <item>They get along perfectly! The poetic, sensitive Fish seeks ways to make the Taurean happy, in exchange for the tenderness and security he needs. They enjoy going out together as well as the intimacy of their home. Their physical love is alchemical, spiritual, and intense. The Bull\'s practical side helps the Pisces to accomplish the projects bubbling up in his or her imagination; a quality which the stolid Taurus needs to lighten his sometimes monotonous life. The outlook for love is promising.</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="compatibility_lookup_table_horoscope_com_2">
        <item>A promise of great excitement and entertainment! Both signs are endowed with good cheer and optimism, which makes them perfect pals. Life together is like an ongoing party, highlighted by flashes of imagination and friendship with others. Gemini easily adapts to the demanding Aries character, while Aries finds his or her partner to be an inexhaustible source of fresh air. The couple lives for the moment, with scarcely a care for tomorrow, but this continual improvisation is not the stuff of which lasting ties are made. Stay tuned for more adventures…</item>
        <item>Gemini is a sociable, gregarious extrovert who loves the bustle of the city, while Taurus is quiet, quaint, and rural. The Bull seeks comfort and tranquillity, whereas Gemini\'s phone is always ringing, much to his or her delight. These fundamental differences may generate misunderstanding and conflict, aggravated by Taurean obstinacy. But the Taurus is easily enchanted by Gemini\'s liveliness, and Gemini finds a Taurus partner provides the security and stability he or she lacks.</item>
        <item>When a dual sign meets up with its alter ego, anything can happen! Optimistic, communicative, and crackling with energy, they zoom along in the fast lane in total harmony. The Gemini sense of humor neutralizes conflicts, native curiosity electrifies their conversations, and their mutual fascination nourishes their love - which thrives on the prodigious sexual imagination they display. Romanticism is not on the menu, but many a spicy dish! The only hazard is their fluctuating nature. But as long as they share the same breeze, there\'s nothing to fear.</item>
        <item>The road looks rocky. Cancer hopes to found a stable, comfortable home for a family; Gemini has an appetite for change, danger, and travel. If he or she feels free to come and go, he or she will appreciate the Crab\'s profound and genuine feelings; in return he or she provides great cheerfulness. Gemini\'s sociability helps the Crab out of his shell. But the latter will always be the first to want to go home to bed. If Gemini can squeeze out a bit of stability, and if Cancer can repress his or her tantrums, they\'ll love each other the way Air mingles with Water.</item>
        <item>Both appreciate extravagance, dazzle, and glitter; the Air of one feeds the Fire of the other. Leo\'s idea of love is grandiose, and Gemini will be fascinated by the attentiveness of his partner. His (or her) curiosity is never satisfied, and the Leo is full of surprises. A helpful hint to the Gemini: be careful of the Leo\'s pride; don\'t arouse his or her ire. Helpful hints to the Leo: rein in your possessiveness, because the Gemini wants to be as free as Air. If these prerogatives are respected, love will be colorful and joyful.</item>
        <item>Signs ruled by the planet Mercury, Gemini and Virgo are busy: one bubbles, while the other is purposeful. Creatures of reason, they can spend hours discussing their work, their friends, and their plans. Virgoan modesty loosens its bonds in the intimate surroundings of the bedroom, whereas Gemini\'s fires tend to burn low. Both are naturally anxious, and they may either reassure each other or, on the contrary, worry each other. This is the key to this cerebral pair, which may benefit from real affinities and an inexhaustible potential for happiness.</item>
        <item>When Air meets Air, love is a breeze. This refreshing, carefree duo sparkles with optimism. Gemini\'s sociability reinforces Libran elegance. In the outer world, they are graceful and entertaining dancing partners, complementing and understanding each other perfectly. They love communication, outings, travel, surprises. Libra appreciates the conjugal bond, but is delicate enough to let Gemini decide for him or herself. In any case, their daily life together is such a joy they are inseparable…</item>
        <item>What a contrast! Airy Gemini and mysterious Scorpio are bound to be an eccentric pair, delighting in their differences. The Scorpion is an intense and intuitive creature, trusting instinct more surely than reason; a detached and lofty Gemini will rationalize and explain. They evolve together with a harmony of purpose, curiosity, and appetite. As long as Gemini is faithful, this pair of opposites will be a source of the greatest thrills of agony and ecstasy - especially in private.</item>
        <item>Air and Fire are a good match. Gemini enjoys Sagittarian finesse, whereas Sagittarius is attracted to this open-minded partner. The couple is likely to lead an exciting social life, surrounded by a vast sea of friends. They\'ll experiment with every form of love. Conversation will thrive on talk of travel and grandiose plans, banishing boredom. The pair will radiate a fresh, youthful feeling of nonchalance, which will attract a horde of friends to share in and magnify their happiness.</item>
        <item>Initially, this would appear to be a poor match: hard-working, ambitious Capricorn clashes with Gemini\'s jovial, carefree spirit. But Capricorn gives mercurial Gemini some needed security, especially financially, while Gemini is a wizard at conjuring away Capricorn\'s worries. If love is present, Gemini\'s adaptability will be an asset in holding on to the Capricorn. He or she knows this is one partner who will never abandon him or her, and that really counts!</item>
        <item>The Aquarian ability to devote body and soul to the cause of justice attracts the respect and love of the Gemini, who will vie to conquer this rare love. Once the two Air signs are united, they will merge into a shared pleasure in action, excitement, and rebellion against stuffy conventions. Together, they believe life gives them the right to freedom and independence. Nothing stops or separates them. Friends as well as lovers, they will unite their souls in making their life into a masterpiece, a great and exciting adventure.</item>
        <item>Pisces swims through deep waters, while the Gemini inhabits the airs. One is a contemplative, solitary being, while the other enjoys discussions. Pisces seeks absolute love and emotional intensity; if the Gemini can stretch his or her imagination to attain the emotional commitment which is alien to him or her, the couple will experience an extraordinary spiritual union. They share a taste for freedom: the Fish to explore his imaginary world, while the Gemini craves a chance to display charisma in the outer world. They may embark on a long journey, or bid each other farewell before casting off.</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="compatibility_lookup_table_horoscope_com_3">
        <item>Sensitive, gentle, subtle Cancer is likely to be offended by the Ram\'s sometimes brutal impulsiveness. One worships the family; the other feels hemmed in by it. Dynamic Aries resents being tied down to the home and hearth primordial to Cancer, and Cancer is likely to withdraw into a prolonged sulk if he or she feels abandoned. Only shared compromise, patience, and attentiveness can build this couple. However, the Aries will always be the boss.</item>
        <item>Could this be the ideal couple? Both partners are unabashed homebodies, delighting in simple pleasures: family life, good food, comfort, and prosperity. They cook up their own candlelight dinners, enjoy quiet evenings alone together, and plan their investments wisely, whether they\'re financial or personal. Mutual enrichment, comfort, and support are virtually guaranteed. They form a self-sufficient couple, a world unto themselves… as long as their home is comfortable and attractive!</item>
        <item>The road looks rocky. Cancer hopes to found a stable, comfortable home for a family; Gemini has an appetite for change, danger, and travel. If he or she feels free to come and go, he or she will appreciate the Crab\'s profound and genuine feelings; in return he or she provides great cheerfulness. Gemini\'s sociability helps the Crab out of his shell. But the latter will always be the first to want to go home to bed. If Gemini can squeeze out a bit of stability, and if Cancer can repress his or her tantrums, they\'ll love each other the way Air mingles with Water.</item>
        <item>Two halves of a romantic whole influenced by the Moon, they will spin a cocoon around themselves and the family they either already have or dream of having. This outer harmony is underpinned by a visceral need for intense emotions, the fusion of bodies, profound union. The Cancerian personality, turned towards the past, is sometimes unhappy in the present. Indulgence, tenderness, and forgiveness are the keys to the changing moods of this Water sign. If the couple separates, each half will wander like a lost soul, until a new love provides a lift.</item>
        <item>The tides of the Moon and the Fire of the Sun… A strange alliance dominated by the Lion\'s strong personality. Leo dazzles, spends, adores. If the Cancerian is too maternal, too watchful over the family budget, or too critical of the Lion\'s extravagance, the latter may feel smothered, the way Water extinguishes Fire. But Leo\'s generosity should charm any Cancer partner. At home, the Lion accomplishes his role with majesty, which can only delight the timid Crab.</item>
        <item>This couple glows with a tranquil aura of harmony. Virgoan organizational skills reassure the anxious Crab, whereas the latter brings Virgo love and imagination. The devoted and dutiful Earth sign will never be wicked enough to push Cancer\'s buttons. The moonchild\'s moods are tolerated and coaxed back to less slippery terrain with patience and rationality, in the affectionate surroundings the Cancerian craves. Their life is orderly and calm, but never dull. They love each other simply, tenderly, and gracefully.</item>
        <item>No doubt the moonchild is enchanted by the Libran\'s sense of harmony and generosity. But lifestyle differences are likely to become insurmountable obstacles early on. Home-loving, maternal Cancer cannot tolerate Libra\'s whirl of parties and entertainment. Libra thrives on company, excitement, communication, networks of relationships. If Cancer cannot broaden his or her social horizons, misunderstanding, irritation, and frustration will ensue.</item>
        <item>Two Water signs dominated by sensuality… their sex life is likely to be thrilling! But is that enough? Cancer and Scorpio share a common craving. Both want to settle down; they claim to be monogamous, and instinctively sense the other\'s emotions. Both are comfortable in the realm of silence. However, Scorpio\'s rudeness may sometimes cause Cancer to recoil; Cancer\'s moodiness may be hard for Scorpio to bear. Moreover, Scorpio\'s overweening selfishness could wilt the strongest Cancerian love. If they endure, their love will be a symphony.</item>
        <item>Water and Fire, the recluse and the globe-trotter, the lecturer and the dreamer… They live in different worlds, but love is an interstellar vessel. Cancer enjoys listening to Sagittarius describe a journey, but will never be coaxed into donning a backpack and embarking on a real adventure. Moreover, the intellectual and physical preferences of a Sagittarius may make it difficult for him or her to strike a resonant chord in a Cancer. It\'s worth a try, but harmony will be hard to achieve.</item>
        <item>A union of talents quite likely to produce harmony. Cancer is delighted to take care of the home and children while Capricorn goes out in the world to earn the family\'s keep. Each helps the other to fulfill an ambition, in realms that are perfectly complementary. The Saturnine personality benefits from Cancer\'s intuition, and the moonchild appreciates Capricorn\'s ability to achieve financial security. They take the time to love, understand, and cuddle each other. An ideal marriage: conventional, happy, and united for life.</item>
        <item>The Aquarian\'s chilly rationality upsets the sentimental moonchild, who craves intense emotion. These two signs are so alien to one another their relationship practically develops an allergic rash on contact. Aquarius values reality; Cancer trusts only intuition. Soon misunderstanding has settled in, widening the gap in the couple. In this struggle, the broken heart is always that of the moonchild. Be forewarned and proceed at your own risk: the stars frown on any union of these two signs.</item>
        <item>When these two Water signs flow together, the Moon soon locks into Neptune\'s orbit. Cancer and Pisces intuitively understand each other; they handle each other\'s sensitivity with respect, care, and gentleness. Their personalities are likely to merge. In physical love, they give of their souls for mutual delight. Loathing power struggles, they silently respect each other\'s solitude, and barely need to speak aloud. Pragmatic Cancer can relieve dreamy Pisces of life\'s daily tasks. If the latter is willing to settle down, total harmony is in store for them.</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="compatibility_lookup_table_horoscope_com_4">
        <item>Aries decides, but the Lion rules. Each must be careful not to offend the other\'s vanity, because the most trivial events can become power struggles. However, the ardor and passion which animate both Fire signs may weld the two individuals into a radiant couple. Adventure, creativity, and success are on the horizon. Love is a matter of tenderness, desire, and submission. But perfect harmony will require respect for Leo\'s pride.</item>
        <item>Birds of a feather flock together, and these two signs have a great deal in common. Deep down, they are erudite, sensual, sensitive, and artistic. Mutual contact reinforces the talent of each. But the extravagant Lion may clash with the discreet and thrifty Bull, and if Leo does not temper his or her selfishness, the Taurean partner will feel hurt. The couple, which is stormy in the intimacy of the bedroom, cannot weather daily life unless each makes a continual effort to accommodate the other.</item>
        <item>Both appreciate extravagance, dazzle, and glitter; the Air of one feeds the Fire of the other. Leo\'s idea of love is grandiose, and Gemini will be fascinated by the attentiveness of his partner. His (or her) curiosity is never satisfied, and the Leo is full of surprises. A helpful hint to the Gemini: be careful of the Leo\'s pride; don\'t arouse his or her ire. Helpful hints to the Leo: rein in your possessiveness, because the Gemini wants to be as free as Air. If these prerogatives are respected, love will be colorful and joyful.</item>
        <item>The tides of the Moon and the Fire of the Sun… A strange alliance dominated by the Lion\'s strong personality. Leo dazzles, spends, adores. If the Cancerian is too maternal, too watchful over the family budget, or too critical of the Lion\'s extravagance, the latter may feel smothered, the way Water extinguishes Fire. But Leo\'s generosity should charm any Cancer partner. At home, the Lion accomplishes his role with majesty, which can only delight the timid Crab.</item>
        <item>When these two Water signs flow together, the Moon soon locks into Neptune\'s orbit. Cancer and Pisces intuitively understand each other; they handle each other\'s sensitivity with respect, care, and gentleness. Their personalities are likely to merge. In physical love, they give of their souls for mutual delight. Loathing power struggles, they silently respect each other\'s solitude, and barely need to speak aloud. Pragmatic Cancer can relieve dreamy Pisces of life\'s daily tasks. If the latter is willing to settle down, total harmony is in store for them.</item>
        <item>Does elegance admit rivalry? Only in this case, where two different realms are involved. One partner is brilliant; the other, refined. The methodical, intellectual Virgoan may sometimes be irked by Leo\'s need to parade. Or, heaving a sigh, submit happily and work behind the scenes to rein in the Lion\'s munificence and extravagance. In exchange, the Virgo receives inalienable, intense, and generous love which is tinged with torrid eroticism. To make the pleasure last, Virgo must overcome his or her legendary anxiety and assuage the Lion\'s every desire.</item>
        <item>Eloquent, artistic, and honest, these two signs share many touchstones and easily accommodate each other elsewhere. The Libran individual, incurably wishy-washy, will adopt the Lion\'s determination if it seems fair. And the Lion laps it up! Leo fulfills the Libran\'s desires, rubbing him or her the right way and expressing boundless love, especially in the physical sense. Friends and lovers, Leo and Libra derive strength from each other to parade splendidly, in dignity and grace, through the outer world. Their love is an intelligent device.</item>
        <item>Riven and driven, this couple wins the passion prize. Leo and Scorpio are locked in a struggle, united on the razor\'s edge. The emotional Leo is offended by Scorpian rudeness; in turn, Scorpio\'s deep feelings are masked by carnal urges. Tension and challenge define this relationship. Each is endowed with an infinite ability to wound or solace the other, and the two will endlessly oscillate between torment and delight. The clash of these two strong personalities is doomed unless indulgence and tolerance also reign. But selfishness may overcome them.</item>
        <item>The Fire signs Leo and Sagittarius pursue the same goals, and can succeed in allying their strengths instead of competing. Optimistic, generous, and romantic, they understand and love each other with both passion and tenderness. They indulge in life\'s pleasures to the fullest, laughing unabashedly and egging each other on. Sagittarian criticism may sometimes hurt the Leo\'s feelings, but forgiveness will soon be forthcoming. The Lion is aware of his sacred complicity with the Centaur-Archer. Together, they reach the heights of bliss.</item>
        <item>Initially, it seems an unlikely match. These two socially-oriented signs often meet at parties and social functions, but rarely cross the threshold to intimacy. Capricorn\'s aridity is almost unable to accommodate the Leo\'s gushy sentimentality and romanticism. Though the Lion enjoys Capricornian humor, the latter\'s independence, self-sufficiency, and smugness quickly arouse his ire. Moreover, extravagant spending is inimical to the Saturnine. If each swallows his pride, the odd couple may succeed. If not, it won\'t…</item>
        <item>The individualistic Aquarian baffles the fiery Leo. The former is fascinated by the future and innovation, whereas the latter will go to great lengths to adopt whatever trend currently prevails. Once they accept their differences, the couple can function as a two-part device. However, their definitions of love are radically opposed: the Lion needs generous helpings of romanticism and sentiment, while the Aquarian rarely acknowledges his emotional side. He or she will think, act, and experiment, but always from a distance, without sentimental commitment.</item>
        <item>Both thrill to the feeling of unconditional love, and their secret sexual garden will bear delicious fruit. However, the Pisces, unconcerned with material things, will treat the Lion\'s gifts lightly. The regal lifestyle and authoritarian character will arouse resistance. The Piscean will not submit; instead, he or she will retreat into an inner world, indifferent to the crashing surf above. The Leo, left alone, will be profoundly wounded. Yet if the Pisces remains by the Leo\'s side, it will be a sign that he or she is finding true emotional fulfillment. And vice-versa.</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="compatibility_lookup_table_horoscope_com_5">
        <item>Virtual opposites: The Virgo is a diligent worker, a faithful partner, and a born organizer; sparkling Aries lacks ongoing commitment but has pizzazz. He may sometimes chafe under Virgo\'s critical gaze. The Ram will dominate the pair, and his or her unpredictability will wreak havoc with Virgo\'s plans. But Virgo gives backbone to the Ram\'s impulses, and guides him or her with valuable advice. The alchemy of opposites forges a constructive but continually strained relationship.</item>
        <item>Two Earth-ruled signs which value tranquillity and discretion, they have all the ingredients for a harmonious love affair. Anxious Virgo finds reassurance in the stolid Bull, whereas the Taurean derives needed peace and energy from the Virgoan. A caress, a gaze, a gesture: each is worth a thousand words, when it comes to expressing the tenderness that binds them together. Taurus dominates, to the delight of clinging vine Virgo. "The power of harmony, and the deep power of joy…"</item>
        <item>Signs ruled by the planet Mercury, Gemini and Virgo are busy: one bubbles, while the other is purposeful. Creatures of reason, they can spend hours discussing their work, their friends, and their plans. Virgoan modesty loosens its bonds in the intimate surroundings of the bedroom, whereas Gemini\'s fires tend to burn low. Both are naturally anxious, and they may either reassure each other or, on the contrary, worry each other. This is the key to this cerebral pair, which may benefit from real affinities and an inexhaustible potential for happiness.</item>
        <item>This couple glows with a tranquil aura of harmony. Virgoan organizational skills reassure the anxious Crab, whereas the latter brings Virgo love and imagination. The devoted and dutiful Earth sign will never be wicked enough to push Cancer\'s buttons. The moonchild\'s moods are tolerated and coaxed back to less slippery terrain with patience and rationality, in the affectionate surroundings the Cancerian craves. Their life is orderly and calm, but never dull. They love each other simply, tenderly, and gracefully.</item>
        <item>Does elegance admit rivalry? Only in this case, where two different realms are involved. One partner is brilliant; the other, refined. The methodical, intellectual Virgoan may sometimes be irked by Leo\'s need to parade. Or, heaving a sigh, submit happily and work behind the scenes to rein in the Lion\'s munificence and extravagance. In exchange, the Virgo receives inalienable, intense, and generous love which is tinged with torrid eroticism. To make the pleasure last, Virgo must overcome his or her legendary anxiety and assuage the Lion\'s every desire.</item>
        <item>Narcissism or partnership? This identical pair may be a whiz at business, but emotional fulfillment is likely to elude them. Together, they contain an overdose of caution, modesty, and dutifulness. However, should they both resolve to put tenderness uppermost, the two Virgoans will communicate well. They share a singular passion for work and common sense which liberates them from many a sentimental or trivial constraint. Both thrive on intellectual activities and may happily spend the day reading or writing. But is that the purpose of love?</item>
        <item>These two emotionally remote signs are likely to strike up an intellectual understanding. They enjoy being together to argue, work, or attend social events. Both are blessed with grace and tact. From the Libran, the Virgo derives the enthusiasm which sometimes fails him or her, but may criticize the other for his endless need to charm. As for the Libran, he or she is liable to be bored. The Virgo partner works so hard he has little time for love. This couple is not easy to construct, but it may thrive once a bond has formed.</item>
        <item>The more the Virgoan probes the Scorpio\'s mysterious personality, the more surprises he or she finds. But the Scorpio\'s display of confidence spirits away the Virgo\'s anxieties. Also, the Scorpio may arouse the Virgo to unexpected frenzies of emotional intensity, especially in bed. These two signs have a great deal to learn from one another. They can observe, understand, and respect each other\'s private sides mutually: one is devoted to mystery and the other to business. And the intensely jealous Scorpio will find the Virgo to be unfailingly loyal and faithful.</item>
        <item>It will take work, but it can be done. The independent character of each, reserved Virgo and exuberant Sagittarius, may thwart all understanding. Confident Sagittarius strides ahead, optimistic and ambitious, whereas anxious Virgo pulls back, careful to avoid danger as much as possible. Sometimes the couple may function as a complementary unit. Thus, Virgoan tact may compensate for Sagittarian frankness, and Sagittarian enthusiasm may banish Virgoan anguish. But basic differences are difficult to overcome, and this couple often succeeds only by an implacable effort of will.</item>
        <item>These Earth signs share the values of hard work, social advancement, and financial security. Although their love may be somewhat arid, they are skillful at climbing the social ladder together, and sustain each other through great effort, with unfailing loyalty. The Virgoan inspires the Capricorn and diverts him or her from a too-serious world; the Capricornian soothes the Virgoan, providing for the couple\'s material needs and freeing the latter\'s wit. If a perfect match existed, this would come close.</item>
        <item>The only turf these two signs can share is the intellectual one. The traditional, methodical Virgo panics in the absence of familiarity and routine; the Aquarius devotes himself to overturning the routine and modernizing the world. Likewise, in the emotional realm, Virgo seeks certainty while Aquarius craves the unpredictable. The Aquarian chill bothers the devoted Virgoan, who may reproach him or herself for some inner failing. However, love makes all things possible… But this couple will be a challenge for both partners to tackle.</item>
        <item>Piscean imagination and poetry provide needed relief to Virgoan common sense, broadening horizons which would otherwise become monotonous. These two individuals share an open-mindedness which would promote discovery, and they may find a way to be happy together. The Piscean can sense the Virgo\'s desires intuitively, which is ideal for their sex life. If the Virgoan respects the Fish\'s mysterious inner depths, he or she will derive great rewards from Pisces. A sense of love is one of the gifts both individuals possess.</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="compatibility_lookup_table_horoscope_com_6">
        <item>Two signs which naturally attract and complement each other. Tactful Libra tones down the Ram\'s fury, and redirects his or her individualism towards a partnership whose logical conclusion is the marriage which matters so much to Libra. The Libran harvests the Ram\'s vigor, but is sometimes rebuffed by blunt language. Aries must be careful to give Libra time to express him or herself. Otherwise, the magnetism which attracts them may turn into mutual repulsion.</item>
        <item>The fact that both signs are influenced by amorous Venus gives their relationship a romantic and sensual outlook. But the sociable Libran\'s appetite for entertainment and conversation may be stifled by the Bull\'s stolid contentment with home and hearth. If the charm is broken, the Libra will soar alone. Moreover, Taurean inarticulateness may repel loquacious Libra. Yet with a little flexibility and subtlety, if these two partners want their relationship to last, it can!</item>
        <item>When Air meets Air, love is a breeze. This refreshing, carefree duo sparkles with optimism. Gemini\'s sociability reinforces Libran elegance. In the outer world, they are graceful and entertaining dancing partners, complementing and understanding each other perfectly. They love communication, outings, travel, surprises. Libra appreciates the conjugal bond, but is delicate enough to let Gemini decide for him or herself. In any case, their daily life together is such a joy they are inseparable…</item>
        <item>No doubt the moonchild is enchanted by the Libran\'s sense of harmony and generosity. But lifestyle differences are likely to become insurmountable obstacles early on. Home-loving, maternal Cancer cannot tolerate Libra\'s whirl of parties and entertainment. Libra thrives on company, excitement, communication, networks of relationships. If Cancer cannot broaden his or her social horizons, misunderstanding, irritation, and frustration will ensue.</item>
        <item>Eloquent, artistic, and honest, these two signs share many touchstones and easily accommodate each other elsewhere. The Libran individual, incurably wishy-washy, will adopt the Lion\'s determination if it seems fair. And the Lion laps it up! Leo fulfills the Libran\'s desires, rubbing him or her the right way and expressing boundless love, especially in the physical sense. Friends and lovers, Leo and Libra derive strength from each other to parade splendidly, in dignity and grace, through the outer world. Their love is an intelligent device.</item>
        <item>These two emotionally remote signs are likely to strike up an intellectual understanding. They enjoy being together to argue, work, or attend social events. Both are blessed with grace and tact. From the Libran, the Virgo derives the enthusiasm which sometimes fails him or her, but may criticize the other for his endless need to charm. As for the Libran, he or she is liable to be bored. The Virgo partner works so hard he has little time for love. This couple is not easy to construct, but it may thrive once a bond has formed.</item>
        <item>As they size each other up, they perceive the other\'s flaws, which they cannot correct since their own are identical. The relationship is swollen with superficiality, because the Libran is reluctant to explore profound emotion. But the couple\'s worldly and glamorous qualities give them a boost. What happens after the guests go home? These two individuals love each other without seeking true union, without engaging in emotional displays, perfectly satisfied with a life oriented towards social events. Be warned that unfaithfulness is quite possible.</item>
        <item>This unusual combination of Water and Air may spawn either the best or the worst. The Libran\'s intellectual grace thrives on the Scorpio\'s emotional profundity, and vice-versa. Libran eloquence may also draw Scorpio out of his silence, and facilitate the Scorpio\'s efforts to make new contacts, although the latter will still need periods of solitude in which to resume his old patterns. The Libran preoccupation with commitment is compatible with the Scorpio\'s possessiveness. Their journey through life together may be long and passionate. This is a union of light and dark.</item>
        <item>The meeting of two such optimistic minds should lead straight to bliss. Together, they enjoy elaborating their plans, consolidating their social prominence, and embarking on adventurous journeys. Librans lean towards marriage, but Sagittarius holds back, fearful of losing his or her independence. However, if he or she can be convinced that marriage will not crimp his or her freedom, the knot will soon be tied. The couple, surrounded by a sea of friends, will carry out shared dreams and ambitions, endowed with just enough common sense and rationality to accomplish them.</item>
        <item>Both value a balanced family life, interspersed with social events in which the graceful Libran attracts admiration while the ambitious Capricorn makes useful professional contacts. But the Libran is liable to be disappointed with the Capricornian concept of love. The latter is so taken up with career considerations that a partner\'s emotional needs are not seen as indispensable. Their love may wilt in this arid climate. Such a couple is soon disunited, with each partner inhabiting a parallel universe, light years from the other.</item>
        <item>When this partnership functions, it thrives as a friendship if not as a passion, growing every day. Both individuals are extroverts who value a busy social life, frequent encounters, and intellectual debate. The Libran looks back with satisfaction on the ground already covered while the Aquarian\'s gaze is riveted on the future. However, the Venusian will have to be patient, because Aquarius is often chilly and fearful of commitment. His or her freedom is too precious; the outer world seems to offer more entertainment than intimacy. But it is worth a try!</item>
        <item>A shared delight in culture, art, and literature gives this Air/Water duo a definite mutual attraction. But the gap between them may soon grow difficult to bridge with understanding. Each must be alert to this fact. A Piscean needs regular doses of solitude, whereas the Libran cannot thrive without the admiration of others. If each respects this basic difference, the Libran can bring the Pisces a pragmatism alien to the latter\'s abstract world. In exchange, the Pisces provides a glimpse of his or her rich imagination - as long as the partner does not probe too insistently.</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="compatibility_lookup_table_horoscope_com_7">
        <item>A bond between these two Mars-ruled signs is ardent, passionate, and often stormy. No neutrality is possible, and day-to-day management of such extreme feelings may prove difficult. Scorpio\'s possessiveness will not tolerate the slightest unfaithfulness, but the Ram often yields fully to the Scorpion\'s sensuality - unless he or she is startled into scampering away… This poignant dance, in which each partner vies for control, can be fleeting or long-lasting, sublime or terrifying: there is no happy medium!</item>
        <item>There\'s a lot of attraction in this match between two naturally reserved, determined, and physically oriented signs, and great potential for domestic success. Both value financial prosperity and hard work. But if they don\'t make beautiful music together immediately, a terrible uproar is imminent. Intuitive, emotional Scorpio accumulates negative feelings until they reach critical mass. If Taurus is not ready to handle a meltdown, Scorpio\'s tenacity will be unbearable and even the Bull will give up. It\'s either heaven or hell: nothing in between.</item>
        <item>What a contrast! Airy Gemini and mysterious Scorpio are bound to be an eccentric pair, delighting in their differences. The Scorpion is an intense and intuitive creature, trusting instinct more surely than reason; a detached and lofty Gemini will rationalize and explain. They evolve together with a harmony of purpose, curiosity, and appetite. As long as Gemini is faithful, this pair of opposites will be a source of the greatest thrills of agony and ecstasy - especially in private.</item>
        <item>Two Water signs dominated by sensuality… their sex life is likely to be thrilling! But is that enough? Cancer and Scorpio share a common craving. Both want to settle down; they claim to be monogamous, and instinctively sense the other\'s emotions. Both are comfortable in the realm of silence. However, Scorpio\'s rudeness may sometimes cause Cancer to recoil; Cancer\'s moodiness may be hard for Scorpio to bear. Moreover, Scorpio\'s overweening selfishness could wilt the strongest Cancerian love. If they endure, their love will be a symphony.</item>
        <item>Riven and driven, this couple wins the passion prize. Leo and Scorpio are locked in a struggle, united on the razor\'s edge. The emotional Leo is offended by Scorpian rudeness; in turn, Scorpio\'s deep feelings are masked by carnal urges. Tension and challenge define this relationship. Each is endowed with an infinite ability to wound or solace the other, and the two will endlessly oscillate between torment and delight. The clash of these two strong personalities is doomed unless indulgence and tolerance also reign. But selfishness may overcome them.</item>
        <item>The more the Virgoan probes the Scorpio\'s mysterious personality, the more surprises he or she finds. But the Scorpio\'s display of confidence spirits away the Virgo\'s anxieties. Also, the Scorpio may arouse the Virgo to unexpected frenzies of emotional intensity, especially in bed. These two signs have a great deal to learn from one another. They can observe, understand, and respect each other\'s private sides mutually: one is devoted to mystery and the other to business. And the intensely jealous Scorpio will find the Virgo to be unfailingly loyal and faithful.</item>
        <item>This unusual combination of Water and Air may spawn either the best or the worst. The Libran\'s intellectual grace thrives on the Scorpio\'s emotional profundity, and vice-versa. Libran eloquence may also draw Scorpio out of his silence, and facilitate the Scorpio\'s efforts to make new contacts, although the latter will still need periods of solitude in which to resume his old patterns. The Libran preoccupation with commitment is compatible with the Scorpio\'s possessiveness. Their journey through life together may be long and passionate. This is a union of light and dark.</item>
        <item>One of the most erotic pairings possible, the Scorpio duo ecstatically merges in the depth of shared emotion. Both endowed with hyperintuitiveness, they sense each other\'s needs without speaking, communicating in an intimate and profoundly aquatic personal language. The only danger they must beware of is their possessiveness, which can undermine their happiness. When jealousy sets in, they can spy on and torment each other into sheer agony. If only this pair of Scorpions could live alone on some deserted island, nothing could trouble their bliss. It would be Paradise!</item>
        <item>Opposites attract, and in this case, Scorpio\'s emotional depth and mystery are intrigued by Sagittarian superficiality and rationality. The Sagittarian is given to idle chatter whereas the Scorpio can spend hours plunged in silence, reading or simply reflecting. When bedtime rolls around, the Sagittarian is looking forward to slumber whereas the Scorpio is ready to uncork his torrid sensuality… Often this sort of couple breaks up soon, after a few epic battles drain the energy of each partner. Exhausting!</item>
        <item>The Scorpio admires Capricorn\'s ambition and determination to reach the top. The earthly realism of the latter complements the aquatic intuition of the former. Mutual respect for a social or mystical quest unites a couple animated by a shared desire for security. Their sex life is vibrant and intense. But their power struggles may be just as passionate. And when these two clash, the sparks fly! Each is too stubborn to make the slightest compromise. If this couple avoids conflict, it can reach great heights.</item>
        <item>The Aquarian flees emotional commitment, whereas the Scorpio swears by it, baffled by his or her partner\'s detachment. Aquarius defines him or herself as the freest of spirits; Scorpio sees love as possession, body and soul. However, as long as Plutonian jealousy is not aroused, this pair can build a mutually satisfying relationship. They respect each other and share a longing for extraordinary experiences. When the tension mounts, each can take refuge in his or her own world until it dissipates. Intuition and cleverness help this couple survive.</item>
        <item>Sensitive and instinctive, Scorpio and Pisces have a mutual affinity only rarely encountered in the zodiac. They may be devoted to one another body and soul; their love is erotic, all-encompassing, and often unique. A gaze speaks volumes of poetry, and intuition replaces reason. Their magical bond is immune to everything except Scorpio\'s jealousy. If it looms, Pisces will dart away on the first wave. He or she loathes ugly emotional confrontations, and this feeling is stronger than his or her passionate love for the Scorpio.</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="compatibility_lookup_table_horoscope_com_8">
        <item>Two Fire signs soar with shared exaltation towards ambitious ideals and adventure. The Sagittarian\'s candor puts the Ram in his or her place if necessary, and communication flows readily between the two, limiting the damage from conflict. Energetic and intimate activity is part of their daily routine. These two individuals have energy to burn, and an appetite for mutual love and seduction. No clouds on the horizon as long as each accepts that the other will make no compromise…</item>
        <item>One dwells in dreamland while the other never takes off from reality; one loves escape, travel, and change while the other doggedly takes root and slowly builds a real accomplishment. Flexible Sagittarius is more adaptable than the stubborn Bull, because he or she uses his or her powers of abstraction as an escape hatch. But each lives in a world alien to the other, and real understanding is a remote possibility. Their fundamental differences are likely to surface one day, perhaps forcefully enough to disunite them.</item>
        <item>Air and Fire are a good match. Gemini enjoys Sagittarian finesse, whereas Sagittarius is attracted to this open-minded partner. The couple is likely to lead an exciting social life, surrounded by a vast sea of friends. They\'ll experiment with every form of love. Conversation will thrive on talk of travel and grandiose plans, banishing boredom. The pair will radiate a fresh, youthful feeling of nonchalance, which will attract a horde of friends to share in and magnify their happiness.</item>
        <item>Water and Fire, the recluse and the globe-trotter, the lecturer and the dreamer… They live in different worlds, but love is an interstellar vessel. Cancer enjoys listening to Sagittarius describe a journey, but will never be coaxed into donning a backpack and embarking on a real adventure. Moreover, the intellectual and physical preferences of a Sagittarius may make it difficult for him or her to strike a resonant chord in a Cancer. It\'s worth a try, but harmony will be hard to achieve.</item>
        <item>The Fire signs Leo and Sagittarius pursue the same goals, and can succeed in allying their strengths instead of competing. Optimistic, generous, and romantic, they understand and love each other with both passion and tenderness. They indulge in life\'s pleasures to the fullest, laughing unabashedly and egging each other on. Sagittarian criticism may sometimes hurt the Leo\'s feelings, but forgiveness will soon be forthcoming. The Lion is aware of his sacred complicity with the Centaur-Archer. Together, they reach the heights of bliss.</item>
        <item>It will take work, but it can be done. The independent character of each, reserved Virgo and exuberant Sagittarius, may thwart all understanding. Confident Sagittarius strides ahead, optimistic and ambitious, whereas anxious Virgo pulls back, careful to avoid danger as much as possible. Sometimes the couple may function as a complementary unit. Thus, Virgoan tact may compensate for Sagittarian frankness, and Sagittarian enthusiasm may banish Virgoan anguish. But basic differences are difficult to overcome, and this couple often succeeds only by an implacable effort of will.</item>
        <item>The meeting of two such optimistic minds should lead straight to bliss. Together, they enjoy elaborating their plans, consolidating their social prominence, and embarking on adventurous journeys. Librans lean towards marriage, but Sagittarius holds back, fearful of losing his or her independence. However, if he or she can be convinced that marriage will not crimp his or her freedom, the knot will soon be tied. The couple, surrounded by a sea of friends, will carry out shared dreams and ambitions, endowed with just enough common sense and rationality to accomplish them.</item>
        <item>Opposites attract, and in this case, Scorpio\'s emotional depth and mystery are intrigued by Sagittarian superficiality and rationality. The Sagittarian is given to idle chatter whereas the Scorpio can spend hours plunged in silence, reading or simply reflecting. When bedtime rolls around, the Sagittarian is looking forward to slumber whereas the Scorpio is ready to uncork his torrid sensuality… Often this sort of couple breaks up soon, after a few epic battles drain the energy of each partner. Exhausting!</item>
        <item>A pair of world travelers with an intellectual bent, they range far and wide in quest of spiritual or physical adventure, with an unsinkable optimism. Explorers, philosophers, athletes: they spend their life on the road and enjoy a vigorous discussion. As for the nest, or putting down roots, neither partner deems such goals worthy of attention. They\'d be happy to live in a tent all their lives; often, their home is just a transfer point. They spend one night there and then set off in quest of new discoveries. But this enthusiastic and curious couple has the key to its own happiness.</item>
        <item>They share values like ambition, success, friendship, and intellectual discussion. But the Sagittarian is optimistic, whereas Capricorn is a pessimist. The former works because he or she must to finance travel, recreation, and leisure activities; the latter could spend his or her life at the office. Soon the Capricorn becomes irritated with Sagittarian glibness, which interferes with concentration. And the latter simply realizes he or she is bored! They may travel together for a time, for each is an independent spirit. But they don\'t understand each other.</item>
        <item>Two adventurous, intellectual signs which share many an affinity. The Aquarian Air fans Sagittarian Fire. They may become active politically, or to save the environment; they discuss philosophy and human rights, and meet a wide variety of people. They never run out of ideas or causes. As for love, they respect, entertain, and enjoy each other. But neither has a taste for torrid passion. They prefer freedom to commitment. Oddly, though, often couples which promise each other nothing stay together the longest.</item>
        <item>Intuitive and independent creatures, they have much to share. Sagittarius can help Pisces make his or her dreams reality, but the former\'s critical mind and frankness may wound the latter\'s hypersensitive nature. They don\'t infringe on each other\'s freedom: each needs something different, and they respect the boundaries at home. But if one partner must submit to the other, it will be the Pisces, who is given to sacrifice. True, the same Pisces, who craves infinite love, may suffer from the Sagittarian lack of passion.</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="compatibility_lookup_table_horoscope_com_9">
        <item>Can a fiery rebel and a practical Earth sign ever reach an understanding? They speak different languages: one held aloft by dreams while the other has his or her feet firmly on the ground. When they know how to reinforce the Ram\'s audacity with the Goat\'s constructive spirit, they can accomplish great things. Capricorn is slow to be tamed and won over, a process which Aries tends to interrupt early if he or she does not control his or her impulsiveness. However, if Capricorn\'s love is allowed to ripen, the other can luxuriate in it forever.</item>
        <item>Courageous, ambitious Earth signs, Taurus and Capricorn seem to be made for each other. Both value financial success and share a love of beauty, of lasting, classical foundations. Capricorn\'s irony charms the Bull, while the latter\'s expert sensuality rescues the Capricorn from his or her natural modesty. They enjoy talking together, and communication is excellent. They confide in each other, promising never to offend or betray the other. This could be a perfect couple.</item>
        <item>Initially, this would appear to be a poor match: hard-working, ambitious Capricorn clashes with Gemini\'s jovial, carefree spirit. But Capricorn gives mercurial Gemini some needed security, especially financially, while Gemini is a wizard at conjuring away Capricorn\'s worries. If love is present, Gemini\'s adaptability will be an asset in holding on to the Capricorn. He or she knows this is one partner who will never abandon him or her, and that really counts!</item>
        <item>A union of talents quite likely to produce harmony. Cancer is delighted to take care of the home and children while Capricorn goes out in the world to earn the family\'s keep. Each helps the other to fulfill an ambition, in realms that are perfectly complementary. The Saturnine personality benefits from Cancer\'s intuition, and the moonchild appreciates Capricorn\'s ability to achieve financial security. They take the time to love, understand, and cuddle each other. An ideal marriage: conventional, happy, and united for life.</item>
        <item>Initially, it seems an unlikely match. These two socially-oriented signs often meet at parties and social functions, but rarely cross the threshold to intimacy. Capricorn\'s aridity is almost unable to accommodate the Leo\'s gushy sentimentality and romanticism. Though the Lion enjoys Capricornian humor, the latter\'s independence, self-sufficiency, and smugness quickly arouse his ire. Moreover, extravagant spending is inimical to the Saturnine. If each swallows his pride, the odd couple may succeed. If not, it won\'t…</item>
        <item>These Earth signs share the values of hard work, social advancement, and financial security. Although their love may be somewhat arid, they are skillful at climbing the social ladder together, and sustain each other through great effort, with unfailing loyalty. The Virgoan inspires the Capricorn and diverts him or her from a too-serious world; the Capricornian soothes the Virgoan, providing for the couple\'s material needs and freeing the latter\'s wit. If a perfect match existed, this would come close.</item>
        <item>Both value a balanced family life, interspersed with social events in which the graceful Libran attracts admiration while the ambitious Capricorn makes useful professional contacts. But the Libran is liable to be disappointed with the Capricornian concept of love. The latter is so taken up with career considerations that a partner\'s emotional needs are not seen as indispensable. Their love may wilt in this arid climate. Such a couple is soon disunited, with each partner inhabiting a parallel universe, light years from the other.</item>
        <item>The Scorpio admires Capricorn\'s ambition and determination to reach the top. The earthly realism of the latter complements the aquatic intuition of the former. Mutual respect for a social or mystical quest unites a couple animated by a shared desire for security. Their sex life is vibrant and intense. But their power struggles may be just as passionate. And when these two clash, the sparks fly! Each is too stubborn to make the slightest compromise. If this couple avoids conflict, it can reach great heights.</item>
        <item>They share values like ambition, success, friendship, and intellectual discussion. But the Sagittarian is optimistic, whereas Capricorn is a pessimist. The former works because he or she must to finance travel, recreation, and leisure activities; the latter could spend his or her life at the office. Soon the Capricorn becomes irritated with Sagittarian glibness, which interferes with concentration. And the latter simply realizes he or she is bored! They may travel together for a time, for each is an independent spirit. But they don\'t understand each other.</item>
        <item>Both ambitious and hard-working individuals, they\'ll put their careers first, well ahead of their romance. Their common sense facilitates daily life and avoids idle arguments. However, their shared drive for success may sometimes be a bit dull and monotonous. In many cases, they prefer to read the newspaper in bed, instead of frolicking together. They take satisfaction in the certainty of having a loyal partner and social and financial success and security. Their relationship is long-lasting and deep, but it places few emotional demands on them.</item>
        <item>Can love bring together two signs which seem to be fundamentally opposed? No doubt, but only for a brief moment until each wakes from a dream of harmony. Career-oriented Capricorn will sacrifice anything to scale the peaks. Imaginative Aquarius thinks only of improving the future of the world and humanity. The former is pragmatic and conservative, whereas the latter is idealistic and rebellious. Capricorn needs a tender, devoted helpmate, and an Aquarian is never home, preferring discussions with buddies to domestic bliss. What more is there to say?</item>
        <item>The profound Pisces sensitivity gravitates toward a solid Capricorn mooring, a reassuring and respectable person. But the total absence of materialism characteristic of the Pisces irritates the Capricorn, who knows what things are worth after having earned them through hard work. Discussion is difficult, due to the Capricorn\'s rock-hard realism. The Pisces floats in a spiritual, emotional, poetic medium. However, often the latter\'s pliancy makes it possible for him or her to submit to Capricorn\'s direction.</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="compatibility_lookup_table_horoscope_com_10">
        <item>Two forward-looking individuals who instinctively understand each other and share a vision of the future, as long as the freedom of each is respected. Aquarius is immune to the Ram\'s domineering spirit. But the Air sign\'s detachment may frustrate the Aries need for passion. If a common interest favors friendship over love and the Ram is satisfied with a dispassionate relationship, while Aquarius gains by the ardent contact with an Aries, the relationship they build will be healthy, fresh, and beneficial.</item>
        <item>Love at first sight is probable, but can it ripen into a lasting love affair? Aquarius has an appetite for freedom and a gaze firmly turned toward the future. The possessive Taurean derives his or her pleasures from immutable values like the land, the family, and the past. If the present brings them together, they rarely evolve in the same direction together, and each will tend to stick to his own character. Soon the Bull feels misunderstood, while the Aquarian dreams of new horizons… But love makes anything possible!</item>
        <item>The Aquarian ability to devote body and soul to the cause of justice attracts the respect and love of the Gemini, who will vie to conquer this rare love. Once the two Air signs are united, they will merge into a shared pleasure in action, excitement, and rebellion against stuffy conventions. Together, they believe life gives them the right to freedom and independence. Nothing stops or separates them. Friends as well as lovers, they will unite their souls in making their life into a masterpiece, a great and exciting adventure.</item>
        <item>The Aquarian\'s chilly rationality upsets the sentimental moonchild, who craves intense emotion. These two signs are so alien to one another their relationship practically develops an allergic rash on contact. Aquarius values reality; Cancer trusts only intuition. Soon misunderstanding has settled in, widening the gap in the couple. In this struggle, the broken heart is always that of the moonchild. Be forewarned and proceed at your own risk: the stars frown on any union of these two signs.</item>
        <item>The individualistic Aquarian baffles the fiery Leo. The former is fascinated by the future and innovation, whereas the latter will go to great lengths to adopt whatever trend currently prevails. Once they accept their differences, the couple can function as a two-part device. However, their definitions of love are radically opposed: the Lion needs generous helpings of romanticism and sentiment, while the Aquarian rarely acknowledges his emotional side. He or she will think, act, and experiment, but always from a distance, without sentimental commitment.</item>
        <item>The only turf these two signs can share is the intellectual one. The traditional, methodical Virgo panics in the absence of familiarity and routine; the Aquarius devotes himself to overturning the routine and modernizing the world. Likewise, in the emotional realm, Virgo seeks certainty while Aquarius craves the unpredictable. The Aquarian chill bothers the devoted Virgoan, who may reproach him or herself for some inner failing. However, love makes all things possible… But this couple will be a challenge for both partners to tackle.</item>
        <item>When this partnership functions, it thrives as a friendship if not as a passion, growing every day. Both individuals are extroverts who value a busy social life, frequent encounters, and intellectual debate. The Libran looks back with satisfaction on the ground already covered while the Aquarian\'s gaze is riveted on the future. However, the Venusian will have to be patient, because Aquarius is often chilly and fearful of commitment. His or her freedom is too precious; the outer world seems to offer more entertainment than intimacy. But it is worth a try!</item>
        <item>The Aquarian flees emotional commitment, whereas the Scorpio swears by it, baffled by his or her partner\'s detachment. Aquarius defines him or herself as the freest of spirits; Scorpio sees love as possession, body and soul. However, as long as Plutonian jealousy is not aroused, this pair can build a mutually satisfying relationship. They respect each other and share a longing for extraordinary experiences. When the tension mounts, each can take refuge in his or her own world until it dissipates. Intuition and cleverness help this couple survive.</item>
        <item>Two adventurous, intellectual signs which share many an affinity. The Aquarian Air fans Sagittarian Fire. They may become active politically, or to save the environment; they discuss philosophy and human rights, and meet a wide variety of people. They never run out of ideas or causes. As for love, they respect, entertain, and enjoy each other. But neither has a taste for torrid passion. They prefer freedom to commitment. Oddly, though, often couples which promise each other nothing stay together the longest.</item>
        <item>Can love bring together two signs which seem to be fundamentally opposed? No doubt, but only for a brief moment until each wakes from a dream of harmony. Career-oriented Capricorn will sacrifice anything to scale the peaks. Imaginative Aquarius thinks only of improving the future of the world and humanity. The former is pragmatic and conservative, whereas the latter is idealistic and rebellious. Capricorn needs a tender, devoted helpmate, and an Aquarian is never home, preferring discussions with buddies to domestic bliss. What more is there to say?</item>
        <item>Soaring together in the jetstream, Aquarius couples fly headlong into the future, improvising day by day. Their high-tech universe is cold and dynamic. Mutual toleration and love for freedom protects them from conflict. They defend causes with an open-mindedness they never outgrow; committing themselves to humanity and attending meetings and rallies. Friends rather than lovers, they attach little importance to sex, and see many other ways of expressing love. Harmony rules over all their activities, which are considerable. A winning team.</item>
        <item>Both signs are attracted to the arts, philosophy, and culture, so they share many ideals. But the Pisces finds the Aquarian lacking in emotion; he or she defines love as an intense experience. The Fish will soon go elsewhere in search of emotional bait. However, if the Aquarian manages to work up a little warmth and tenderness, the couple can evolve towards great intellectual and imaginative accomplishments. It\'s a matter of balance and availability. Pisces demands little time, which is perfect for the busy Aquarian. But if Pisces is denied affection, he or she will take off in search of it.</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="compatibility_lookup_table_horoscope_com_11">
        <item>Pisces has a fleeting and almost solitary spirit which may provoke the Aries authoritarian tendencies, and the two signs do not soothe each other. Pisces readily submits to domination, since he or she is awash in an inner world where reality has little effect. The vitality of Aries provides needed security. The couple will function if the Ram surrounds the Pisces with constant affection. If not, the Fish will spawn elsewhere, without even turning around for a final farewell.</item>
        <item>They get along perfectly! The poetic, sensitive Fish seeks ways to make the Taurean happy, in exchange for the tenderness and security he needs. They enjoy going out together as well as the intimacy of their home. Their physical love is alchemical, spiritual, and intense. The Bull\'s practical side helps the Pisces to accomplish the projects bubbling up in his or her imagination; a quality which the stolid Taurus needs to lighten his sometimes monotonous life. The outlook for love is promising.</item>
        <item>Pisces swims through deep waters, while the Gemini inhabits the airs. One is a contemplative, solitary being, while the other enjoys discussions. Pisces seeks absolute love and emotional intensity; if the Gemini can stretch his or her imagination to attain the emotional commitment which is alien to him or her, the couple will experience an extraordinary spiritual union. They share a taste for freedom: the Fish to explore his imaginary world, while the Gemini craves a chance to display charisma in the outer world. They may embark on a long journey, or bid each other farewell before casting off.</item>
        <item>When these two Water signs flow together, the Moon soon locks into Neptune\'s orbit. Cancer and Pisces intuitively understand each other; they handle each other\'s sensitivity with respect, care, and gentleness. Their personalities are likely to merge. In physical love, they give of their souls for mutual delight. Loathing power struggles, they silently respect each other\'s solitude, and barely need to speak aloud. Pragmatic Cancer can relieve dreamy Pisces of life\'s daily tasks. If the latter is willing to settle down, total harmony is in store for them.</item>
        <item>Both thrill to the feeling of unconditional love, and their secret sexual garden will bear delicious fruit. However, the Pisces, unconcerned with material things, will treat the Lion\'s gifts lightly. The regal lifestyle and authoritarian character will arouse resistance. The Piscean will not submit; instead, he or she will retreat into an inner world, indifferent to the crashing surf above. The Leo, left alone, will be profoundly wounded. Yet if the Pisces remains by the Leo\'s side, it will be a sign that he or she is finding true emotional fulfillment. And vice-versa.</item>
        <item>Piscean imagination and poetry provide needed relief to Virgoan common sense, broadening horizons which would otherwise become monotonous. These two individuals share an open-mindedness which would promote discovery, and they may find a way to be happy together. The Piscean can sense the Virgo\'s desires intuitively, which is ideal for their sex life. If the Virgoan respects the Fish\'s mysterious inner depths, he or she will derive great rewards from Pisces. A sense of love is one of the gifts both individuals possess.</item>
        <item>A shared delight in culture, art, and literature gives this Air/Water duo a definite mutual attraction. But the gap between them may soon grow difficult to bridge with understanding. Each must be alert to this fact. A Piscean needs regular doses of solitude, whereas the Libran cannot thrive without the admiration of others. If each respects this basic difference, the Libran can bring the Pisces a pragmatism alien to the latter\'s abstract world. In exchange, the Pisces provides a glimpse of his or her rich imagination - as long as the partner does not probe too insistently.</item>
        <item>Sensitive and instinctive, Scorpio and Pisces have a mutual affinity only rarely encountered in the zodiac. They may be devoted to one another body and soul; their love is erotic, all-encompassing, and often unique. A gaze speaks volumes of poetry, and intuition replaces reason. Their magical bond is immune to everything except Scorpio\'s jealousy. If it looms, Pisces will dart away on the first wave. He or she loathes ugly emotional confrontations, and this feeling is stronger than his or her passionate love for the Scorpio.</item>
        <item>Intuitive and independent creatures, they have much to share. Sagittarius can help Pisces make his or her dreams reality, but the former\'s critical mind and frankness may wound the latter\'s hypersensitive nature. They don\'t infringe on each other\'s freedom: each needs something different, and they respect the boundaries at home. But if one partner must submit to the other, it will be the Pisces, who is given to sacrifice. True, the same Pisces, who craves infinite love, may suffer from the Sagittarian lack of passion.</item>
        <item>The profound Pisces sensitivity gravitates toward a solid Capricorn mooring, a reassuring and respectable person. But the total absence of materialism characteristic of the Pisces irritates the Capricorn, who knows what things are worth after having earned them through hard work. Discussion is difficult, due to the Capricorn\'s rock-hard realism. The Pisces floats in a spiritual, emotional, poetic medium. However, often the latter\'s pliancy makes it possible for him or her to submit to Capricorn\'s direction.</item>
        <item>Both signs are attracted to the arts, philosophy, and culture, so they share many ideals. But the Pisces finds the Aquarian lacking in emotion; he or she defines love as an intense experience. The Fish will soon go elsewhere in search of emotional bait. However, if the Aquarian manages to work up a little warmth and tenderness, the couple can evolve towards great intellectual and imaginative accomplishments. It\'s a matter of balance and availability. Pisces demands little time, which is perfect for the busy Aquarian. But if Pisces is denied affection, he or she will take off in search of it.</item>
        <item>A boundless ocean of feeling and spirit hosts the emotional and physical exchanges of two Pisces individuals. They mirror each other\'s personalities, attracting each other, merging at every depth, intuitively understanding each other. Each senses the other\'s flow, without interfering. Respect for individuality rules. Their daily life may be somewhat erratic and unrealistic, but if they are artists, they will evolve together in a world of emotion, tenderness, and philanthropy. Their sexuality will be sublime, as each seeks to please the other. Exquisite devotion…</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>